On Wings of Eagles is a drama, history, war film
directed by Stephen Shin Kei-Yin.
Eric Liddell - China's first gold medalist and one of Scotland's
greatest athletes - returns to war-torn China.
Eric Liddell, played by Joseph Fiennes.
Xu Niu, played by Shawn Dou.
Florence Liddell, played by Elizabeth Arends.
Dr. Hubbard, played by Richard Sanderson.
Gentleman, played by Darren Grosvenor.
Chen Quan, played by Simon Twu.
On Wings of Eagles (also titled The Last Race) is a 2016 historical sports drama film directed
by Stephen Shin and Michael Parker and starring Joseph Fiennes and Shawn Dou.
An American-Hong Kong-Chinese co-production, the film is an
unofficial sequel to Chariots of Fire  (1981).
The film explores themes of sports, prisoner of war, based
on true story, japanese occupation of china.
The tone is emotional.